To give you the best possible experience, this site uses cookies. Continuing to use videodeck.net means you agree to our use of cookies.

Privacy Policy
==============

COMCODE d.o.o., as the owner of this website, created this privacy statement to demonstrate our commitment to the privacy of our visitors and customers. As a company, we strictly adhere to all industry guidelines and we continually review our policy and procedures to ensure the safety and protection of our customer information. There follows an explanation of our commitment to protecting the privacy of Internet Users.

Information Collection and Use

COMCODE d.o.o. is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from those which are disclosed in this statement. COMCODE d.o.o. collects information from our users at several different points on our website.

Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the users hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.

Cookies on our site

We use Google Analytics (just like virtually everybody else) a service provided by Google. They gather anonymous data of how people are using this site and then provide us with visitor statistics, details of page views etc etc. If you are anti-Google you can opt-out of being tracked by Google Analytics at [http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) (we’d prefer you didn’t though as this data is seriously helpful to us in improving our website and to provide a better experience for you!) The cookies which Google places on your computer are called: \_utma, \_utmb, \_utmc and \_utmz. Check [Google privacy site](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) for an overview of privacy at Google.  
  
This is a list of basic information about cookies used on our site:

|     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| #### Cookie Name | #### Duration the cookie is on your computer | #### When Can I delete the cookie myself? |
| \_utma | 2 years | Whenever you like! |
| \_utmb | Less than 1 Day | Whenever you like! |
| \_utmc | Deletes itself when you leave our website | Whenever you like! |
| \_utmz | 6 Months | Whenever you like! |
| Session | Deletes itself when you leave our website | Whenever you like! |
| PersistentCookie | 1 Year | Whenever you like! |

If you don't like cookies you can get instructions for deletion on [following page](https://www.wikihow.com/Clear-Your-Browser's-Cookies).

Log files

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track site use, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we Comcode d.o.o. are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

Security

This website takes every precaution to protect our users information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, the information is protected both online and off-line. While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our user information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information.

Third Party Services

This website uses data provided by Third Party Services. Each of these Third Party Services may have Terms of Services, Privacy Policies, Community Standards, and other customer obligations that also apply when connecting via this website. You can find the links to these policies below. By using this website you are also agreeing to be bound by Third Party Services Terms of Use.  

Main data source provider on this website is [YouTube API Services](https://developers.google.com/youtube/v3).

Deleting stored data and Revoking of access

This website is accessing users Authorized data provided by Google OAuth. To revoke access to Authorized data you can visit [https://security.google.com/settings/security/permissions](https://security.google.com/settings/security/permissions).

* [\[email protected\]](https://www.videodeck.net/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Copyright © 2012-2024 [COMCODE d.o.o.](https://www.comcode.si/) All Rights Reserved.

2012-12-20     [Follow us on Google+](https://plus.google.com/110480686492183952339) RATING:

4.12 ( 838 ratings)

Price: from 0.00 to $9.99 

Video Deck for YouTube™ Easiest way to follow videos of your favorite YouTube subscriptions.
